Personal Training Healthy U Evaluation																				
Submission Details			Questions																	
Serial	Time	Instructor	1. Instructor is enthusiastic about class.	"2. Instructor's overall knowledge, organization, and expertise."	3. Instructor gives clear instruction and exhibits propery body mechanics.	4. Instructor treats participants equally and respectfully.	5. The facility and equipment were clean and well-maintained.	6. The classes were held at convenient times.	7. The class met your expectations.	8. The fees for class were fair.	9. You are gaining more fitness knowledge through this class.	"10. Participation has provided you with noticeable benefits such as balance, fitness, and stress management."	11. Participation has expanded your interest in staying fit and healthy.	12. The class helped with a total feeling of well-being.	13. Participation has provided you with skills and abilities that would serve you well after college.	14. You would consider taking another Healthy U Fitness class offered through Intramurals & Recreation.	How did you hear about this class?	What did you like most about this class experience?	What did you like least?	Comments/suggestions
1	03/27/2012 - 4:58pm		4	4	3	2	4	5									word of mouth			
2	03/27/2012 - 5:00pm		5	5	5	5	5	5									Not sure			
3	04/27/2012 - 2:53pm	Anne Sobol	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	Website	Having to be accountable motivated me to actually go to the gym. Anne was GREAT! 	The Bellefield gym's hours when school isn't in session	-
4	04/27/2012 - 3:52pm	Stephanie Sudjian	1	1	2	1	5	3	1	1	1	1	1	1	1	1	internet	not much	"The lack of structure
My trainer would say she would send me weekly workouts and then never would until I reminded her at least 2
No real progression
Didn't learn what I wanted to learn
"	hire trainers that aren't too busy or don't give them as many clients
5	04/27/2012 - 9:50pm	Aaron Kurtz	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	from the pitt website	I obtain my goals		
6	04/28/2012 - 12:43am	Anne Sobol	4	4	5	5	3	5	4	5	4	4	5	4	4	5	A flyer I saw in Student Health	The price was very affordable. 	I was told the price will be increasing. 	"I am assuming that option #5 is supposed to be ""strongly agree"", not ""strongly disagree"""
7	04/28/2012 - 8:15am	Laura Feree	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	my.pitt.edu	"Laura! Going to the gym can be very intimidating, Laura changed that for me. She was very approachable she really took into account what I wrote on my goal sheet and catered the workout to what I wanted to achieve...and I did!"	nothing Laura is the best trainer ever!	
8	04/28/2012 - 5:05pm	Anne Sobol	4	5	5	4	4	5	3	3	5	4	4	3	5	1	I heard about it through the Healthy Fitness Web page.	"The swimming sessions were the best part of the class.  My trainer, Anne, taught me how to swim for fitness purposes.  She really helped me improve my form and showed me different exercises I can do in the water.  This class also introduced me to gym equipment.  I feel like I can workout on my own, now."	"I had scheduling issues with my first trainer, Steph.  She was pretty inconsiderate, canceling on me and waiting until the last minute to change the time.  It seemed as if she had a lot on her plate, but it was still not what I was expecting.  I expected something more professional.  Her work outs were very good, though.  My second trainer's cardio workouts weren't fantastic.  I felt as if they didn't push me very much.  HOWEVER, as said above, the swimming sessions were excellent."	Create more uniform programs. There was a great deal of variation between trainers.
9	04/30/2012 - 12:34am	Travis DiLeo	4	5	4	4	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	"Student Health Services, where I am employed"	I truly had a personalized training experience. Travis was very aware of my goals and created a fitness plan based specifically around my goals and my current level of fitness.  He also provided workouts that I can build upon as I continue to work out after the training sessions have ended.		
10	04/30/2012 - 12:57pm	Laura Feree	3	5	5	5	4	5	4	4	4	3	5	5	4	4	Pitt website	I was given a variety of exercises that I could complete on my own after our sessions ran out.	No post-assessment	
11	05/08/2012 - 9:29am	Joe Kolano	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	5	poster in gym	personal training- great flexibility in schedule-- 	my achin' body after joe got through with my sorry a#$%	great program- thanks pitt for offering - 